anthropologie.com 2016-04-14

# US Security Help | Anthropologie

## Privacy & Security — United States

Updated October 2012

### Your Privacy

Thank you for shopping at anthropologie.com. This privacy and security policy (“Policy”) outlines the information we collect about you, how we use the information and the choices you have to review, revise and/or restrict our usage of this information. 

### Collected Information

Anthropologie.com collects customer information for a variety of reasons, including as part of our ongoing efforts to provide superior customer service, improve our customer's shopping experience and to communicate with our customers about our products, services and promotions, including those that we believe may be of particular interest to you based on information we have collected. We collect personal information such as your name, financial information, telephone number, e-mail and postal address (“Personal Information”) that you provide to us when you save your information with us or when you participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey. We use this information to process any transaction, inquiry or promotion that you initiate with us, and provide you with advertising tailored to your interests. In addition, we maintain a record of your product interests, purchases and whatever else might enable us or our business partners to enhance and personalize your shopping experience on this or other websites and to provide you with offers, promotions or information that we believe may be of interest to you. We also monitor use of the Website and traffic patterns to improve the Website design and the products and services we offer as well as to determine what offers, promotions or information to send to you.

Anthropologie.com may disclose specific personal information about you if required by law, governmental request or court order, if based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court. We may also disclose information about you to other members of the Anthropologie corporate family, as well as a company contracted to help prevent the unauthorized use of credit and gift cards.

*You can easily update your account information by logging on to anthropologie.com and clicking Your Account

### Our Email List

We offer those who sign-up for our email list advanced notice of sales, new merchandise, store openings and other anthropologie news. Email addresses collected at Anthropologie.com are used internally and by our business partners. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email list or would prefer that your email address not be shared with our business partners, [click here](http://ebm.cheetahmail.com/r/regf2?aid=1134998097&n=200&a=0) or contact us. We will remove your name from our email list within a reasonable period of time. Please recognize that you may receive another email before we are able to remove you.

### Our Catalog Mailing List

If you no longer wish to receive Anthropologie catalogs, please contact us or call [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500). Please include your name and mailing address as shown on your catalog. We will remove your name from our mailing list as soon as possible. Please recognize that you may receive another catalog before we are able to remove you.

We may, on occasion, share a portion of our catalog mailing list with our business partners. If you do not want your name and address shared with other organizations, contact us or call [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500).

### Business Partners

Anthropologie contracts with outside service providers to help us better understand your use of anthropologie.com. Our service providers place cookies on your computer or use other technologies to collect various kinds of information for us related to your use of anthropologie.com, so that we and our business partners may continue to refine and improve the site and other sites for our customers, and provide advertising tailored to your interests. We do not allow our service providers to collect any credit card, user name or password information. As a visitor to anthropologie.com, you may opt out of being included in this collection of data by contacting us or calling [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500). To opt-out of third party advertising tailored to your interests, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). We may also use our own cookies to deliver enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of this advertising provided directly by Anthropologie, click [here](http://dtmc.anthropologie.com/adinfo/adchoices_fpc.html?cid=2466&cname=Anthropologie&cmagic=7b41bf&clogo=anthropologie.png&purl=www.anthropologie.com%2Fanthro%2Fhelp%2Fprivacy_security.jsp%27,%27_blank%27,%27status=0,toolbar=0,location=0,menubar=0,directories=0,scrollbars=1,width=921,height=758).

“Cookies” are bits of information that are automatically stored on your computer. If you do not want to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser to disable them.

We or our partners may use Flash Cookies (also known as Local Stored Objects) or other similar technologies. A Flash cookie is a small data file placed on a computer using Adobe Flash or similar technology that may be built into your computer or downloaded or installed by you to your computer. We use these technologies to personalize and enhance your online experience, facilitate processes, personalize and store your settings. Flash cookies may help our website visitors to, for example, set volume preference associated with a video experience, play games and perform surveys. They help us improve our sites by measuring which areas are of greatest interest to customers. They may be recognized by other sites or by our marketing or business partners. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies and the cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. [Click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/) to learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies or other similar technologies, please be aware that you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable.

We also use other methods of automatic collection to determine information about visitors to our website, including the IP address, browser, language preferences, and computer identification numbers. We use the information obtained using these tools to provide better customer service, enhance our product offerings, and detect potential misuse or fraud. To opt out of any such data collection, contact us or call [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500).

### Secure Shopping

Sensitive personal information contained in orders placed on the Website are encrypted using 128-bit secure sockets layer (SSL) technology.* In order for SSL security to work, you must use an SSL enabled browser. *Secure Socket Layer (SSL) is a technology used by vendors to ensure the security of online business. It negotiates and employs the essential functions of mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity for secure transactions.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect you Personal Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Website cannot be guaranteed; (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party; and (d) WHEN YOU TRANSFER ANY INFORMATION TO US, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK.

If you still have concerns about ordering electronically, feel free to call [800-309-1500](tel:800-309-1500) and place your order over the phone. Have the 8-digit style number, size, and color ready for each item you wish to order. You can also print your shopping basket page and mail it to:

Anthropologie  
4010 Rose Lane  
Augusta, GA 30907  
Attn: Order Processing 

Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. We will never ask for sensitive information via email.

* Secure Socket Layer (SSL) is a technology used by vendors to ensure the security of online business. It negotiates and employs the essential functions of mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity for secure transactions. 

### Policy Changes

Anthropologie.com may periodically update this Privacy & Security Policy for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here. By visiting our website you agree to accept any changes made to this policy. The anthropologie.com Privacy & Security Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website.

Feel free to contact us with any questions about our Privacy & Security Policy.

Email | [service@anthropologie.com](mailto:service@anthropologie.com)  
---|---  
Phone | [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500)  
Fax | 800.474.8858.  
Mail |  Anthropologie  
4010 Rose Lane  
Augusta, GA 30907  
Attn: Customer Service   
  
## Privacy & Security — Canada

Updated December 2012

### Your Privacy

Thank you for shopping at Anthropologie. Ensuring the privacy and security of your personal information is very important to us. Our Privacy & Security Policy outlines the information we collect about you, how we use, disclose and otherwise manage this information and the choices you have to restrict our usage of this information.

This Privacy & Security Policy applies to personal information we collect from our Canadian customers at Anthropologie retail stores in Canada, through our website located at www.anthropologie.com and through other interactions with our Canadian customers.

### Collected Information

We collect personal information when you purchase, order, return or exchange products and services; sign up for anthro or our email or catalogue mailing list; purchase a gift card; visit or register on our website; apply for a job at Anthropologie; tell a friend about one of our products or services; participate in a promotion or survey; or contact us with a comment, question or complaint.

### Shopping at Anthropologie

You do not have to provide us with any personal information when you purchase merchandise for cash at one of our stores. If you use a credit or debit card for any of your purchases, we collect your credit or debit card-related information and your signature for the purposes of processing your payment.

### Anthro

If you sign-up for anthro, we may collect personal information such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number and birth date. We use this information to communicate with you and provide you with useful services and special benefits.

### Our Email List

We offer those who sign-up for our email list advanced notice of sales, new merchandise, store openings and other anthropologie news. Email addresses are only used internally for the purpose of sending you these emails. We respect your privacy rights and will not sell or rent your email address to other companies without your consent. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email list, [click here](http://ebm.cheetahmail.com/r/regf2?aid=1134998097&n=200&a=0) or contact us as set out in the “Contact Us” section below. You may also click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails.

When you sign-up for our email list, we may also may collect optional information such as your name, postal code, and product interests. We use this personal information to tailor our email messages and to enhance our product and service offerings.

### Catalogue Mailing List

If you sign-up for our catalogue mailing list, we collect your name and mailing address. If you no longer wish to receive Anthropologie catalogues, please contact us at [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500) or service@anthropologie.com. Please include your name and mailing address as shown on your catalogue.

We will remove your name from our mailing list as soon as possible. Please recognize that you may receive another catalogue before we are able to remove you.

### Gift Cards

When you purchase a gift card, we collect your name, billing address, the address for delivery, phone number, email address, credit card information, amount of the purchase, and a username and password. We use this information to process and fulfill your gift card order.

### Visit or Register on Anthropologie.com

You do not have to register to visit anthropologie.com. To take advantage of certain services, you may choose to create an account by providing us with your email address and a password that you select. Personal information you provide to us while creating or updating an account and at checkout on our website (such as name, address, telephone number, email address, billing address, ship-to address and credit card information) is maintained in electronic files on our web server and our internal systems located in the United States. Your registration information is used solely to provide and otherwise administer the services you requested, unless you otherwise consent.

### Optional Information

We may collect optional demographic and/or preference information. We use this information to tailor or improve our product and service offerings, as well as for internal marketing research purposes.

### Apply for a Job

If you apply for or enquire about a job at Anthropologie, you may provide us with personal information about yourself, such as that contained in a resume or similar employment-related materials. We use this information for the purpose of processing and responding to your enquiry or job application.

### Tell A Friend

If you send an email to a friend through our website to tell them about one of our products or services, we collect you and your friend’s name and email address as well as any message you provide. We will not use you or your friend's email information for any other purpose. Please only send emails to friends or family who would want to receive the message.

### Promotions and Surveys

When you participate in a promotion or respond to one of our surveys, we may collect your name, address, phone number and email address. We use this information to administer your participation in the promotion and, for surveys, to contact you with follow-up questions.

### Customer Service

When you contact one of our customer service representatives with a question, feedback or other comment, you may be asked for information that identifies you, such as your name, address and telephone number. We collect this information to verify your identity and to help us promptly answer your question or respond to your comment or feedback. We may retain this information to assist you in the future. We also may use your feedback, suggestions and comments to monitor and/or improve our products or website.

### Website Information Collected

You can visit anthropologie.com without telling us who you are or providing us with any personal information. However, we collect the IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all our website visitors and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our website. We use this information to monitor and improve our website.

We use cookies and similar technologies to collect product and purchase information from the pages you access or visit. Cookies are bits of information that are automatically stored on your computer so we can recognize you when you return. We use cookies to better understand your use of anthropologie.com so that we may continue to refine and improve the website for our customers. If you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser preferences to disable them. However, if you decide not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features on anthropologie.com. The information collected through cookies may be combined with other identifiable personal information (such as demographic and past purchase information) from our records and other sources. We may use this combined information for future marketing initiatives and to help us improve our website presentation and your overall shopping experience.

### Third Party Links and Advertisements

Our website may provide links to third party websites. Except as provided herein, we will not provide any of your personal information to these third parties without your prior consent. Anthropologie provides links to third party websites as a convenience to the user. The inclusion of any link does not imply Anthropologie's endorsement of any other company, its websites, or its products and/or services. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies, which we recommend you read carefully. We have no control over such websites and therefore have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose and otherwise treat your personal information.

We may also use third parties to serve Anthropologie advertisements on other websites. In order to measure the effectiveness of our advertisements, these companies may use tracer tags or web beacons to report certain information (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to anthropologie.com and the websites which advertise and feature links to anthropologie.com.

### Social Media

We may offer you the opportunity to engage with our content on or through third-party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications. When you engage with our content on or through third-party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information associated with your social media account (e.g., name, username, email address, profile picture, gender) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the website, plug-in or application. When you provide information from your social media account, we may use this information to personalize your experience on our website and on the third-party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications, and to provide you with other products or services you may request.

### Information We Share

We may transfer (or otherwise make available) your personal information to other members of the Anthropologie corporate family and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. We may use service providers to process data and online payments, deliver our products and services, host our website, send emails, run our promotions and surveys, help us better understand your use of anthropologie.com and refine and improve the website.

All of our service providers are required to maintain the confidentiality and security of your personal information and to use it only in compliance with applicable privacy laws. These companies are not authorized to use your information in any manner, other than in helping us to provide you with products and services or as otherwise required by applicable law. For information on the manner in which our service providers treat your personal information, please contact us as set out below.

Your personal information may be stored and processed in the United States by our affiliates and other third party service providers.

### Secondary Marketing

We may obtain your permission to share your contact information with carefully selected marketing partners who may contact you by mail or email with offers about products and services that may be of interest to you. You will be able to remove your name from such marketing lists at any other time by contacting us at [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500) or service@anthropologie.com. You may also click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails.

### Legal

Please note that Anthropologie must provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required by Canadian or US law. We may also disclose personal information to assist us in collecting a debt owed by you, or otherwise where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

### Sale of Business

Anthropologie may transfer any information we have about you in the event of a merger with a third party or upon a sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party acquirer.

### Retention of Personal Information

We only keep your personal information as long as necessary for the purposes we collected it, or as otherwise required by law.

### Security of Personal Information

Your privacy is important to us. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against the loss, theft, unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. We have implemented measures in an effort to safeguard the personal information in our custody and control, including only providing access to personal information to employees and authorized service providers who require such information for the purposes described in this Privacy & Security Policy.

To provide you with an increased level of security, online access to certain personal information may be protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication.

### Phone and Fax Orders

If you do not wish to shop through our website, feel free to call [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500) and place your order over the phone. Have the 6- or 8-character style number (ex. 923451 or 12755555), size and color ready for each item you wish to order. You can also print your shopping basket page and fax your order to [800-474-8858](tel:800-474-8858) or mail it to:

Anthropologie  
30 Industrial Park Blvd.  
Trenton, SC 29847  
Attn: Order Processing 

Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. We will never ask for sensitive information via email.

### Policy Changes

Anthropologie.com may periodically update this Privacy & Security Policy for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here. We will treat your personal information in accordance with the Privacy & Security Policy in place at the time your information was collected.

### Contact Us

Feel free to contact us with any questions about our Privacy & Security Policy or the manner in which we treat your personal information or to withdraw your name from an email or other marketing list.

If you wish to access or update the personal information we have about you, or to correct factual errors in our records, please contact us as set out below. To protect your privacy, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You can also easily update your account information by logging on to anthropologie.com and clicking my account.

Email | [service@anthropologie.com](mailto:service@anthropologie.com)  
---|---  
Phone | [800-309-2500](tel:800-309-2500)  
Fax | 800.474.8858.  
Mail |  Anthropologie  
4010 Rose Lane  
Augusta, GA 30907  
Attn: Customer Service 
  *[GA]: Georgia
  *[Attn]: Attention
  *[SC]: South Carolina
